BILLY (YUNTING) SHAO

shaobilly@gmail.com | +1 (306)515-4650 Regina, Saskatchewan S4W 0P6

BIOGRAPHY

Billy is a creative Technology and computer science student in the Department of Media, Art and Performance student at the University of Regina, in Saskatchwan. He was live and worked in two Canadian provinces as an web designer, writer and Photographer. Yunting's practice blurs boundaries between expert-amateur, hobby-work, and leisure-productivity. He was work hard for his school work and he use his spare time to study various 3d modeling software and electronic painting technology. His works have been included as examples in the electronic painting and artificial intelligence curriculum proposal guidance plan of Chinese universities.

EDUCATION

University of Regina Expected in 12/2022

Undergraduate: Computer Science

Courses: C Programming, Embedded Systems, Computer Network and Communication, Computer Control System.

University of Regina Expected in 12/2022

Undergraduate: Creative Technology

Courses: Art design, Audio make up, After effect.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Teaching assessment, University of Regina Faculty of Media, Art and Performance

01/2022 to 04/2022

- Supported classroom maintenance and upkeep, organizing books and materials.
- Set up visual aids, equipment and classroom displays to support teacher's lesson delivery.
- Assisted teachers with classroom management and document coordination to maintain positive learning environment.

 Distribution Clerk. Great Asian Market

 05/2021 to 08/2021
- Documented stock records and schedules accurately.
- Scheduled pickups and deliveries to maintain smooth operations.
- Accelerated consumer purchasing habits by increasing distribution and availability across range of retail outlets.

Food Deliverer, Skip The Dishes

04/2017 to 01/2021

- Completed on-time deliveries by choosing best and most efficient routes.
- Verified daily deliveries against shipping instructions before delivering to customers.
- Kept detailed records of completed or in-progress deliveries using hand-held devices and camera images.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Programming: C/C++, C#, Python, Java, CSS

Art Design: Adobe Photoshop, Charting and graphing

Database: MySQL, SQL Server Language: Chinese, Japanese, English